## **ALLISON NAULT**

Email: allisonrnault@gmail.com | Phone: 616-204-2600 | Chicago, IL

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/allison-nault-b64354246/

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/allisonnault">https://github.com/allisonnault</a> | Portfolio:

# **Summary**

A highly motivated team leader with 2 years of professional sales experience in the fitness industry. A top performer able to leverage Hubspot CRM tools to increase productivity, ensure quality standards, and implement best practices. Experienced in overseeing multiple departments, training staff, and developing team members.

# **Technical Skills**

JavaScript. CSS, HTML, SQL, NoSQL, GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Express, Node, Handlebars, JQuery, Bootstrap

# Other Skills

Customer service and sales

Managing multiple departments

· 2 years CRM experience

Payroll processing

Employee training and development

· Sales and outreach management

Client account management

Scheduling

# **Projects**

# **Experience**

02/2020 - 01/2023 Regional Operations Manager

Brooklyn Boulders Full Time

Chicago, IL April 2022 - January 2023

- Supported product growth by ensuring programs, classes and other offerings were properly staffed and scheduled
- Oversaw group fitness & personal training, climbing programs, youth programs, retail, customer experience, and front desk operations for two Chicago Facilities.
- Prepared and submitted bi-weekly payroll for two facilities (~84 employees).
- Facilitated monthly staff scheduling at two facilities to ensure maximum efficiency and productivity of all team members.
- Directly managed and supported the Customer Experience
  Team responsible for responding to online service requests.

## **Lead Community Advisor**

**Full Time** 

January 2021 - April 2022

- Built a collaborative sales team culture with a focus on training, coaching, and implementing best practices to unleash potential of sales representatives to maximize results.
- Created workflows and automations within Hubspot CRM to improve guest traffic management and membership sales
- Increased national membership base ~3x to 10k active members between April 1 - September 2021, achieving best sales months ever in company history in Q2 of 2021.

## **Community Advisor**

Full Time

August 2020 - January 2021

- Leader in membership sales, averaging 30+ sales/ month
- Proficient in using Hubspot CRM for sales outreach and lead management

### **Front Desk Operations**

Full Time

February 2020 - August 2020

- Implemented stringent COVID-19 safety protocols, delivering 40,000+ unique guest check ins in 2H 2020 without any reported virus transmission within facilities.
- Provided customer service to guests and members, including

check-ins, facility orientations, retail POS, and COVID screenings

- Opening and closing procedures
- Helped with Facility cleanliness
- Climbing instruction and personal coaching

# 07/2012 - 02/2020 Beadniks Chicago Chicago, IL

## **Retail Store Manager**

#### Full Time

- Managed store appearance, including merchandising and displays, signage, decorations and cleaning.
- Delivered excellent customer service by greeting and assisting each customer.
- Shared product knowledge with customers while making personal recommendations.
- Updated and edited store website.
- Interviewed, supervised and trained employees.
- Oversaw inventory management.
- Stocked and restocked inventory when shipments were received.
- Instructed workshops on jewelry making techniques.
- Constructed custom jewelry designs for customers and the store.
- Worked closely with jewelry designers to fabricate their designs.
- Oversaw daily cash register operations.
- Went on buying trips to bead and gemstone conventions.

# 08/2011 - 05/2012 **Co- Instructor** After School Matters Chicago, IL

## Part Time

- Worked with high school students to create a multi-media, mosaic mural for George Washington High School.
- Taught basic design, mosaic, painting and sculpture techniques.
- Oversaw fabrication and installation of the mural.

06/2011 - 08/2011

**Assistant Instructor** 

Chicago Public Art Part Time

Group Chicago, IL

- Worked in partnership with After School Matters to create Aqua Interlude and Reflection, a 1,500-square-foot mosaic for the city of Chicago located in the Columbus Drive underpass to the Museum Campus.
- Aided lead artists in teaching students how to cut and set mosaic tiles.
- Assisted in the installation of the mosaic.

# **Education and Training**

2023 **Certificate in Full Stack Web Development** 

Chicago, IL Northwestern University & edEx

2011 Bachelor of Fine Arts in Sculpture and Printmaking

Elmhurst, IL Elmhurst College